Step 1: click (78, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The navigation tabs are visible near the top of the page.
Step 2: click (90, 306) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The navigation tabs are visible
Step 3: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The 'Code' tab is alrea
Step 4: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The README is already v
Step 5: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see we are on the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The README is
Step 6: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. Looking at the current screen, I can see the README is alr
Step 7: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see we are on the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The README is
Step 8: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see we are on the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The 'Code' ta
Step 9: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see we are on the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The README is
Step 10: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see we are on the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The README co
Step 11: done  [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for pphouse/screenpilot. The README tab is currently active (visible at the top of